<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Projects on Chris Mony</title>
        <link>ch-mon.github.io/projects/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Projects on Chris Mony</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="ch-mon.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Fashion recognition</title>
            <link>ch-mon.github.io/projects/fashionrecognition/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>ch-mon.github.io/projects/fashionrecognition/</guid>
            <description>During quarantine, some friends and me decided to tackle a exciting project. It was centered around training a Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) to recognize certain fashion articles in Instagram pictures. The final goal was to find relevant posts from influencers and create a keyword which potentially generates more traffic the next days and can be used for GoogleAdWords Marketing.
We started with the Google Open Image Database and trained a Yolo-V3 CNN in Google Colab to recognize different fashion articles (e.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>During quarantine, some friends and me decided to tackle a exciting project. It was centered around training a Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) to recognize certain fashion articles in Instagram pictures. The final goal was to find relevant posts from influencers and create a keyword which potentially generates more traffic the next days and can be used for GoogleAdWords Marketing.</p>
<p>We started with the <a href="https://storage.googleapis.com/openimages/web/index.html">Google Open Image Database</a> and trained a Yolo-V3 CNN in Google Colab to recognize different fashion articles (e.g. dresses, shoes, &hellip;) on several thousands of pictures. Afterwards, we&rsquo;d scrape some influencer pictures from Instagram and would classify them whether they contain fashion articles. After cropping and detecting the main color of the item, we decided to give out a keyword in the form of &ldquo;(Influencer name) (main color) (fashion articel)&rdquo; (e.g. &ldquo;Adele Blue Dress&rdquo;). Afterwards, we&rsquo;d map this result to GoogleTrends via an Python-API and check for any significant peaks in the search interest. Lastely, we also played around with setting up a small front-end for the CNN using steamlit.</p>
<p>The total pipeline which we used can be summarized in the following way:</p>
<p>TO conclude, for me this project was a fascinating chance for learning. One had to dig into differnt solutions for the different challenges which arouse during the development and I was able to strenghten my skills in web-scraping, utilizing state-of-the-art ML models, APIs and front-end development.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Learning phase transitions with Machine Learning</title>
            <link>ch-mon.github.io/projects/phasetransition/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>ch-mon.github.io/projects/phasetransition/</guid>
            <description>The first principal component shows hifh correlation with the order parameter.
  Background This project is concerned with the work of my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s thesis. During the four months, I investigated the phase transition of the Ising model with machine learning and applied the same methodology to another statistcal model. Hereby, apart from a pratical course during the studies, I had never worked with machine learning before, so this was a great opportunity to dig deeper into the topic.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<figure class="center">
    <img src="../OrderParameterRodModel.png"
         alt="The first principal component shows hifh correlation with the order parameter." width="600"/> <figcaption>
            <p>The first principal component shows hifh correlation with the order parameter.</p>
        </figcaption>
</figure>

<h2 id="background">Background</h2>
<p>This project is concerned with the work of my <strong>Bachelor&rsquo;s thesis</strong>. During the four months, I investigated the phase transition of the Ising model with machine learning and applied the same methodology to another statistcal model. Hereby, apart from a pratical course during the studies, I had never worked with machine learning before, so this was a great opportunity to dig deeper into the topic. Also, the thesis formed my first real contact with the Python programming language.</p>
<h2 id="project-description">Project description</h2>
<p>First, we began by reproducing the previous work of other researchers (<a href="https://journals.aps.org/pre/abstract/10.1103/PhysRevE.96.022140">Wetzel, 2017</a>; <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/1803.08823">Metha et. al., 2018</a>) and learned the order parameter of the 2D Ising model. Hereby, we relied on two different approaches: <strong>Principal Component Analysis (PCA)</strong> and <strong>Variational Autoencoders (VAEs)</strong>. In the next step, we applied exactly the same methodology to another physical model, the so-called rod-model (<a href="https://aip.scitation.org/doi/abs/10.1063/1.4960618">Oettel et. al., 2016</a>). For both models, the configurations needed as training data was generated by <strong>Markov-Chain-Monte-Carlo (MCMC)</strong> sampling.</p>
<h2 id="results">Results</h2>
<p>We were able to show, the even for the new model, the machine learning methods are able to extract the order parameter by themselves (see plot above).</p>
<h2 id="learnings">Learnings</h2>
<p>For me, the thesis provided an excellent opportunity to explore the domain of machine learning. For me, the most important learnings were:</p>
<ul>
<li>Programming
<ul>
<li>Python &amp; corresponding packages
<ul>
<li>Numpy, Matplotlib, Keras, Scikit-Learn</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Anaconda</li>
<li>Linux Shell interaction</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Methodological
<ul>
<li>Unsupervised machine learning</li>
<li>Principal Component Analysis (PCA)</li>
<li>Variational Autoencoders (VAEs)</li>
<li>Markov-Chain-Monte-Carlo (MCMC) sampling</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="code">Code</h2>
<p>The code I used for my thesis can be found in <a href="https://github.com/crizzle94/Bachelor-thesis">this GitHub repo</a>.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
