<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Mony</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chris Mony</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About the practical application of values</title>
      <link>/blog/values/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/values/</guid>
      <description>My value wall. I blurred the details since some texts are quite personal. If you want to know how I define a specific value, simply ask me;) However, if you are really interested in my style of formulating them, I included the template for two banners (including text) at the bottom.
  While I was bike touring last year, I happened to stumble (i.e., pedal :D) into the beautiful city of Stockholm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack4Good</title>
      <link>/projects/hack4good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/hack4good/</guid>
      <description>Hack4Good Banner. Photo from the H4G website.
  Background During my time at ETH Zurich, my team (big shout-out to Frederike Lübeck, Kaoru Schwarzenegger, and Vincent Bardenhagen) and I had the chance to participate in the two-month-long sustainability Hack4Good program. This hackathon was organized by the Analytics Club and the Student Project House (SPH) at ETH. Five teams would be presented with challenges and data offered by different NGOs and solve the former within the given timeframe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts from a fellow traveller</title>
      <link>/blog/thoughtsfromafellowtraveler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/thoughtsfromafellowtraveler/</guid>
      <description>Fully loaded bike in front of Lund University.
  Last year, I traveled by bike for three months. Everything I needed, I could fit either into one of my four bags or over the rack (as you can see above). Even though it feels like I experienced more during those three months than during a typical year, the days were quite routinized. Wake up, meditate, have breakfast, pack the tent, cycle for 70-120 km, search for a spot to spend the night, set up the tent, have dinner, write journal, and fall asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Chris (actually Christoph, but simply call me Chris) and I warmly welcome you on my website. If I had to summarize myself in one sentence, it would be the following: I am a character who is driven by a strong passion for learning &amp;amp; utilizing the newest technologies (it is crazy what is currently happening out there), while on the other hand trying to retain balance in the fast-paced environment of our today&amp;rsquo;s world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal</title>
      <link>/personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 13:32:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/personal/</guid>
      <description>If you look it up on Wikipedia, Curriculum Vitae loosely translates from Latin as course of life. As Wikipedia continues to know, it usually refers to the complete record of someone&amp;rsquo;s career. However, as much as I believe that work is a crucial part of our lives, for this website, I will refer back to the original meaning. By doing so, I will reach beyond a classical CV and express the course of my life by drawing a more wholesome picture - including important stations and most shaping moments of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion recognition</title>
      <link>/projects/fashionrecognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/fashionrecognition/</guid>
      <description>Watch Classification. Photo by Eliud Gil Samaniego.
  Background During quarantine, some friends (Pano Herbe and two more) and I decided to tackle an exciting project. It was concerned with training a Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) to recognize certain fashion articles in Instagram pictures. The final goal was to identify fashion objects from Instagram influencers, create potentially traffic-generating keywords, and use them for Google Ads marketing. This service would be especially valuable for data-driven fashion retailers who want to increase their click-through and conversion rate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reads</title>
      <link>/reads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 15:34:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reads/</guid>
      <description>Here are some books, I managed to read over the years. It is crazy how fast it adds up and how the knowledge becomes larger than the sum of its parts by making connections. Currently, I am still trying to figure out when to re-read or re-listen to books, but as a good quote says
 I cannot remember the books I&amp;rsquo;ve read any more than the meals I have eaten; even so, they have made me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning phase transitions with Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/projects/phasetransition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/phasetransition/</guid>
      <description>The first principal component shows high correlation with the order parameter.
  Background This project is concerned with the work of my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s thesis. During the four months, I investigated the phase transition of the Ising model with machine learning and applied the same methodology to another statistical model. Hereby, apart from a practical course during the studies, I had never worked with machine learning before. Thus, this was a great opportunity for me to dig deeper into the topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>N.E.S.T. project</title>
      <link>/projects/nestproject/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/nestproject/</guid>
      <description>Logo of the nestbau AG. Photo taken from the nestbau website.
  Background During my time with the student consultancy InOne Consult e.V. in Tuebingen, I had the chance to work on several exciting projects. Amongst one of them was developing a Social Media Marketing Strategy for a local real estate investment fund. The N.E.S.T.bau AG (short nestbau) plans, builds, and rents out flats in the Tuebingen region under the guidance of ethical principles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>